Hey.
Hey, Gary.
Hi, John.
Tired.
But you are back home?
Hmm.
Yep.
In one of my homes.
Huh?
You have more than one home.
No, we're moving, but we haven't moved.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Hey, Wade.
Hello.
So are you all set up for Monday?
Monday?
They don't even tell you these things?
No.
I have filled out the hundred forms or so that they have, and then they sent me another email after saying I was done saying, oh, you have another hundred to do, so I'll do those in the morning.
Okay, so you're not all set.
The guys are on vacation until the 24th.
So I would just use next week to make sure all your VPN and shit is taken care of.
Yeah, I mean, it's just, I'll fire off an email, bill an hour or two for it, whatever.
Yeah.
Just 80 hours, right?
Like, not a whole lot.
Yeah.
Some pizza and beer money.
We're all spending on my new 3D printer.
You have a 3D printer?
I bought a boron kit and I've just been grinding away on it for the past two weeks.
One of those assemble it yourself for 40 hours plus.
You from my house.
I don't see any dicks.
Are you sure you're in Santorini?
Oh, sorry.
Just ignoring.
Just ignore it.
You're not on headphones, Costas?
No, not yet, because everybody's asleep.
Sorry.
Just don't.
The dick jokes can be kept to a minimum.
Just to a minimum today.
Okay.
Just today.
Actually, you could go with the dick jokes.
This is Greece.
They probably won't notice.
Stephan, I approve of your shirt.
Oh, thank you.
What does this shirt say?
I don't know.
It looks really appropriate.
A good barbarian shirt.
Yeah.
It's actually a samurai.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
It is.
Oh, from like ninja scrolls or something.
It could be a samurai, barbarian samurai.
Who knows?
It doesn't sound right when you say it, but anyway.
Let me just get.
Okay.
So let me just bring up the summary so I can remind myself.
I don't know whether the rest of you remembered what happened last week, but I just woke up, so it doesn't hurt for me to remind myself.
Okay.
Yes, I don't know what's going on.
Okay, so there were a bunch of things you guys wanted to do.
So.
I need to get my torto soup.
I picked a name for the band.
Ooh.
You did?
Lathander's death.
Lathander's what?
Death.
Okay.
Controversial.
To death battle ban with Anders death.
Yeah.
Couldn't possibly have any other meanings.
All right.
So, where we left our part, where we left our party off, they had a dinner with the Lord Protector to prepare for, a dawn performance, the Spire of the Morning Lord to deliver, a private meeting with Lord Cassian as his residence to arrange, and a growing mystery surrounding a dead noblewoman, a missing gnome, and a broken interplanar shipping device.
Their next stop would be the counting house, house where a letter of recommendation waited to open doors into the disrupted supply chain of the Lionshield Coster.
Never Winter, it seemed, was never going to let them rest.
All right.
So the plan was to start with the Lionshield Coster, if I recall correctly.
The Counting House?
Yes, the Counting House.
Sort out some supply chain issues or.
Well, so just to remind you what happened, just to remind folks, Linnane, who Greywind was, had a franchise.
That's what we call it in the real world of the Lionshield Coster coster.
Now, just to be clear, it's not a franchise, you know, it's part of a merchant guild.
That's what we call it these days.
And so she was being, what you learned was that she was being supplied by some kind of interplanar dimension device that reduced cost of shipping goods to practically zero until it stopped working until it stopped working.
And now she's been reduced to doing things the old-fashioned way and moving goods around.
And there was, and so, what a shame, what a shame.
And she suggested to Brewbarry that, you know, perhaps he could go to the counting house to find out, you know, whether there's how there's anything that could be done about the supply chain issues and whether there was a way to move supplies, et cetera, et cetera.
So that was the intent of going to the counting house, which is to find how exactly will I move my soft, cuddly, adorable bathrooms.
Yes.
All right.
Do it.
Uthgardtian barbarians used to be all about this hack and the slash and the violence and the whatnot.
Brewbarry wants to make it about the
Soft bathrobe.
He wants everybody needs a break, you know, in life.
Self-care.
What's the best way to take a break then to put on your soft bathrobe, just chill and relax?
Chill and relax, right?
Especially when you're over your push, of course.
Yes, I mean, that's you ever go into battle with the bathrobe?
Yeah, I was going to ask, is the bathroom over or under the dragon scale armor?
Man, it could be a concept, but then you'd risk staining it with blood and shit.
So probably not.
Oh, it's all right.
How many of the damn times?
Sorry?
Well, you can always wash it, right?
No, barbarians don't wash their clothes now.
I'm not familiar with that concept.
This is a revelation.
We're not familiar with that concept.
You'd have to explain to you.
You could use mending as long as you do it while I'm not watching.
Okay.
All right.
What good is it to wash your barbarian clothes when you're going to get them dirty in the next few hours or days or minutes or whatever?
A few hours.
That sounds right.
Yeah.
There's no point.
Just no point.
Just keep it as it is.
Plus, you call it dirt.
I call it sweat and blood.
That's what we barbarians live for.
All right.
Not on your bathrobe.
Got it.
Okay.
Just not on the bathrobe.
Absolutely.
All right.
So I presume you arrive at the counting house.
As you arrive at the counting house, Vukradin, of course, is very excited because he has the let he has a con he has this conference free letter of credit.
Don't forget that he acquired from his mind payout.
Brewbarry, right?
No, I thought you also had the letter of credit.
That's something I have a letter of credit.
Hold on.
Let me just make sure.
The mine paid something?
Hold on.
I'm just making sure.
I got it right.
Who would have thought?
You know, gold mine pays off.
I don't think we got that.
I guess we didn't go down that path.
Sorry.
We turned to page 72, not to page 13.
Doesn't sound super familiar.
I have a letter of introduction to the counting house that Linnane gave me.
I guess the letter of credit is for later.
So you won't need it because we're going to be filthy rich from all the donations that we're going to collect in Neverwinter.
You mean the charitable foundation will be filthy rich.
Yes, absolutely.
Yes.
That's exactly what I mean.
That's exactly what you meant.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll give you one more second.
Okay.
All right.
So I walk into the counting house and my booming voice and I say, hello, good folks.
I am Brewbarry Root Smasher Ogoro.
No, sorry.
Yes.
Oh, okay.
Yes, I remember that.
Okay.
I bring here a letter of introduction from Linnane, and I've heard that you are having some trouble with the supply chain and something that maybe I can help with.
Who are you talking to?
Well, hold on.
Nobody here.
There's nobody here, Brewbarry.
Really?
Damn.
I had prepared that speech in my bathrobe last night.
I rehearsed it for like 15 minutes.
Okay, so what?
It was a good one.
You know, if you want, I can give you some tips on how to be more persuasive.
I've got a silvery tongue, which I do not have.
My axe is my tongue.
Well, it's quite a good speech.
You just need to remember to wait for people to enter the room, and then you start.
Well, where are they?
Where is everyone?
Okay.
So you walk into it inside.
The counting house is, you know, it's a typical medieval typical bank for a fire for high-end industrial, for high-end industrialists.
You walk in, there's a lot of tables, and someone notices you and says, Hello, hello.
My name is Andrell.
My name is Andrell B.
Vance.
How can I help you?
Andrell B.
Vance?
Yeah.
Did I get that right?
Andrell B.
Vance?
Sounds like some of our space brand.
Some weird pun that we're missing.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
Andrell Vance.
That sounds a little better.
Andrell.
Okay.
All right.
That's what I'm Andrell.
I just told you what I said.
It goes hard.
Okay.
All right.
This is Brewbarry's moment.
Go for it.
Yes.
This is your lucky day, Andrell.
My halberd and my friends here are here to sort out your supply chain problems.
We don't have a supply chain problem.
Aha, have I been lied to then?
Here's a letter of introduction by Linnane, whatever her name is.
She's my wealth management consultant.
And she told me she couldn't move around my bathrobes because he goes, oh, what are you making again?
Mr.
Bikusi sits and says, Mr.
Brewbarry, first of all, I think your costume is wonderful, and I really admire the cosplaying of it.
But it's costume.
Now, speak very slow here, Andrell.
Use your next words very carefully.
I have a question.
Oh, yes.
What do you count?
Yeah, this is a counting company.
The leaf I'm off.
Oh, Mr.
Vukradin?
Yes, I am Vukradin, and we are Lathander's death.
I'm sorry, I don't know what that.
It's our man, Lathander's death.
But yes, but Mr.
Vukradin, I was speaking to Mr.
Speaking to me.
Let's not get sidetracked.
Yes, but I'm doing business with Mr.
Yes.
One moment.
I do have a piece of paper for you too, Mr.
Vukradin.
I'm really delighted that you came by.
But let me help Mr.
Brewbarry first, if that would be okay with you.
You're not going to help me.
I'm going to help you, old man.
Don't get things confused in your little that little head of yours.
Now, please tell me, is there some business to be done here?
Or should I go elsewhere?
Well, what are you making?
What do you mean, what am I making?
Am I supposed to tell you what I'm making?
Yes, this is this letter of letter of intro.
Yes, well, so what the letter says is that you.
are that Linnane is saying that she wants us to lend her money so that she can start her business but she doesn't describe the nature of the business I'm supposed to be toughness to the world this world is and I'm getting toughness to to all the people all the good people of the forgotten realms by providing them with supplying them with bathrobes ah well that sets that's very interesting he takes a little piece of paper quill and starts scribbling some notes down and how do you know how much this will cost to make i have absolutely no idea which is why i have a wealth management consultant i suggest that you talk to her ah well very well i i will make a note of talking to her and how do you intend to ship your goods what do i look like some merchant you know a logistics uh guy no i act and slash she's an idea of what you want me to do here oh gosh he goes he goes oh i see you intend to use Lionshield Coster as your shipping agent and business arrangement oh yes of course how silly of me mrs linn here points out finally you're starting to think all right let's get this going please he goes i'm sorry i he pauses he goes mr mr brewbarry i i wish to apologize i want you to know that i have no objection to lionshield coster's business or their interest in in and and and and i i've done wonderful business with them but their rights have gone ridiculously up and i'm afraid that based on my calculations and he pulls out like you know well he pulls out some calculations that you can't read so what a few seconds ago he didn't know what i was making and now he has huge list of calculations well i mean it's it's you don't know what he has he you can't read i mean if somebody else wants to read it it's it's yeah are you sure his name is not texas instrument no it can count pretty fast there's a data we'll just call him tax from now on that's right so here he he presents a small piece of paper right so he scribbles it down he says well i will have to double check the numbers but unfortunately i i have to be honest with you with the margins we expect uh even with milinane's very generous uh margins and prices and the cost of man moving goods in and out of vandaline plus and he starts going i don't think i i feel that the the county house let me let me let me cut you off you know you've been yada yada yada yada you get my blood pumping just just tell me you're gonna get it done and that's it otherwise i'm gonna get upset you're not you're not tallying in want to see me upset you're not tallying in two additional factors yes the temple markup and the churchill lathander's uh bulk uh uh demand something oh he looks at you he goes ah oh you are one of the blessed of lathander then he pauses and goes and you're a drow we're but you're very perceptive andre he goes well but mr brewberry i wish to inform you that i do have a solution to your problem that's what i want to hear i you wouldn't let me i i realize you're this is very agitated and i realize you've already made business arrangements with you've already made some early business arrangements with lionel uh lionel coster's agent linen greywin but since your business is in production what i would suggest you do is instead of using line shield coster for uh distribution of goods you reach out to housemargaster they're the ones who have managed to reduce the pricing of goods quite significantly and i believe with their margins and their arrangements you would be able to run the business most efficiently and if you could secure a letter of uh agreement with them uh a letter of agreement with them we would be more than delighted to sign under on the dotted line do i look like a fool tell me mr mr mr blueberry do i look like a fool andre you know
I'm clutching my halberd and just tapping it in my other hand.
He looks no, so no, exactly.
So, what did I tell you?
Who is Linnane?
She is your wealth advisor.
I'm not saying exactly.
And you tell me to go and do some business with somebody else.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, Mr.
Vubert.
I think I'm an idiot.
Do you have like some sweet deal with this other guy?
I didn't give two shit about it.
I told you, I have a wealth management consultant.
She has a supply company.
She's going to borrow money from you.
You're going to lend it to her, and you're going to get this done.
Okay.
Surely there's an interest rate that you would find acceptable given the increased risk of a lower margin distributor.
We can come to some sort of arrangement there, right?
Plus, I've send you the 2016.
17.
Yeah.
I also find it a bit strange that she had this technique to get her prices down for supplying things.
And then suddenly she tells me that she's got some supply chain issue that I should talk to you about.
You tell me you don't know about it.
And then you point me to this other guy who has found a way to magically get his costumes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, Mr.
Brewbarry.
And Mr.
Vukradin, I think your concerns are legitimate, but I would be remiss.
I would be remiss as I look, if what you wish to do is to borrow.
Remiss you're going to be if you continue down this path, my friend.
You keep talking.
You need to stop doing stuff.
Stop talking to me.
Go do what you got to do.
I see.
So, Mr.
Brewbarry, I felt as your banker, it was my duty to offer you a better path.
But if you wish to do business with the Lionshield Coster, are you my wealth management consultant?
Are you?
Oh, you're the money man.
So, what you're going to do is give us money so that we can do business.
Very well, Mr.
Brewbarry.
That's what I want to hear.
As you wish, you want to be my friend, Andrell.
Yes, he goes to me.
Meanwhile, there's a little bit of a crowd looking at you.
Right.
You kind of.
There's a bit of a crowd surrounding you at this point in time.
And he signs the paperwork.
He gives you the paperwork for the loan.
So you've decided.
So he gives you the paperwork for the loan, which is quite significant, but we'll be able to kickstart your business with Linnane.
Will be able to kickstart your cheap business.
So now let's go back to the topic of Linnane's supply chain issues.
Are you sure you don't know anything about it?
Because she told me you would.
Unfortunately, all I know is that there was some kind of system that Lionshield Coster was using that stopped working some time ago for reasons that are obscure and apologetic.
But you'd have to go consult House Margaster if you wanted to learn more.
I personally just know that as a result of this sudden change in their shipping methods, the prices of goods shipped by Lionshield Coster has gone up considerably and their business.
This is how you do business, you know?
You send people left and right?
No, no.
So you're going to go to House Margaster.
You're going to find out what's going on.
And I'm going to come back tomorrow and you're going to tell me how I can fix it.
You get it, Andrell.
You're going to earn the money that I'm going to give you.
So just as a type of, you do have a lead at what else might be broken.
So I just want to make sure.
I just want the rest of you.
Brewbarry, I love your things to do.
We've got a list of quests to do in Neverwinter, long like my halberd.
One of them is actually a lead.
One of them is actually a lead on House Margaster.
Is it?
Yes.
They're evil.
Weren't they champions?
Yes.
Anyways, we probably told you to.
Stephan, just add a character for a moment.
House Margaster was a recurring villain as a recurring villain in these campaigns.
Okay.
They are all Moriarty, you mean?
Yes, they're Moriarty.
Yeah.
Okay.
Moriarty.
Moriarty had it.
Moriarty had class, though.
Oh, they don't?
Just to be clear, they are recurring.
Anyway, it doesn't hurt to get multiple angles.
So you're going to go to this house and you're going to find out.
Yes, you are.
No, I was about to say yes.
You're going to do it.
And I'm going to come back and you're going to give me what I need.
Got it?
Absolutely, Mr.
Good job.
See, you'd like your role intimidation.
I just want to know what you get.
Intimidation.
12.
All right.
Decent.
Yes.
All right.
I'm glad I know what that number is.
Do I really need to roll?
I mean, you know, I tower over this little guy who probably his most exciting day in his life was when he went on a house.
Clearly, he has advantage, right?
Clearly.
And he goes, he goes, well, Mr.
Brewbarry, I intend to find out what I can buy tomorrow.
You can rely on the counting house.
I'm a barbarian.
I don't know much about business, but when something, when some wheels turn, you oil it.
That's what we put in.
At this point in time, hold on.
Hold on, Brewbarry.
At this point in time, you see some client of the counting house who kind of sort of looks dressed like you, but like, whereas you've got like real barbarian hides.
Cheap cosplay!
No, it's worse than that.
It's fruity cosplay.
Oh, geez.
Are they mocking him?
No, no.
This is, you know, some very wealthy dude who's decided to, you know, wear Uthgardtian barbarian clothes, but instead of being made from hides, it's made from silks, you know, that kind of thing.
All right.
And he walks up to you and he goes, what a genuine costume.
He goes.
I'm touching my clothes.
Be careful.
Wow, you are really into the bit.
I am very impressed.
And then he tries to mimic you.
It's very awkward for a moment there.
All right.
I just ignore him.
So, yes, you have, so you, you, yes, you okay, so you'll come back tomorrow to see what are you going to find out?
And in the meantime, we can go on about other business.
Can I ask?
I didn't find out what they count.
Money.
How?
Monet?
He goes, the counting house is a bank.
Oh, and Mr.
Okay.
Well, yes.
Oh, you could have just said you're a bank.
All right.
We count money.
I thought they count notes or count beats in a measure.
They didn't specify.
Yeah.
It's a mystery.
All right.
So, but meanwhile, so the Andrell, after being after that ordeal, turns to Vukradin and says, Ah, Mr.
Vukradin, there appears to be a notice of credit for you.
From the Neverwinter Commission, from the Mountain Toes Mine.
Oh, yes.
The mine.
Yes, yes.
But you'll have to go collect it from those two, from that table over there.
Okay.
And there again, you're doing it, Andrell, and pointing people left and right instead of doing it yourself.
Why don't you go?
Oh, my friend.
Because this is unfortunately a different department, Mr.
Brewbarry.
I do loans.
They do fulfillment.
You see my halberd, you see my Axe.
They have two different departments as well.
And you're about to meet them both.
Brewbarry, Brewbarry.
He's not our servant.
He's not a slave.
Well, he's a banker.
We're in a bank.
He's a bad banker.
He's not good at his job.
I'll give you that.
But he's not a slave, and we can't order him around.
He looks at you.
He looks, Mr.
Vukradin.
I want to thank you.
Mr.
Brewbarry, I wish you to know that you have the County Council's full financial support and banking going forward.
But I really unfortunately cannot supply this information.
Mr.
Vukradin, I'm happy to walk you over and make the introduction.
Yes, I'm a Chinese wall between departments.
Yes, yes.
Chinese wall.
What would the term actually be?
A an interdimensional wall, a planar barrier.
You know, I'm no businessman, but if I have some advice to give you, you know, you got to think differently.
Like, you know, it's not my problem.
It's somebody else's.
He's over there.
Go talk to him.
That doesn't work.
Maybe it's like a firewall or a wall of fire.
Wall of fire, planar barrier.
Firewall, wall of fire.
All right.
So you arrive at the table, and to your surprise or horror, you see the same comedy routine from the Falcon's Lodge.
Oh, oh, it's those guys.
It's our friends.
We have a letter for them.
Yes.
They're working at Sank.
Apparently, yes.
And it says, it's a cue.
It's a small folding table with a velvet rope and a cue of zero purple, which says, Rimardo and Mr.
Corin, divine accountants and occasional entertainers.
Very occasional.
I mean, accounting now.
Wow, they've really sunk low.
Jeez.
Oh, hey, guys.
We know you.
We have a letter for you.
We were actually looking for you.
Ah, yes.
Rimardo looks at you.
Yes, we've been waiting for you for some time.
He pulls up the paper and he looks through a book.
He starts flipping through it.
And then he goes, pauses.
I'm here to audit your moral economy.
All of a sudden, Corin starts producing receipts from every place you've ever been, like handing them out.
He literally brought receipts.
Right.
I got it.
From the Bronze Sun as well.
No, no, not from me.
Finally, Rimardo picks up one of the papers and looks at it.
You have not refused dirty money.
You have merely laundered it through paperwork with better penmanship.
And you notice he's staring at the UBT.
What?
Who's dirty money?
I'm just telling you what he's.
And then you also notice that Corin has produced the subcommittee charter that was just produced.
Finally, Corin looks, Marta looks at it, looks at you and says, Well, do you have anything to say?
I've got this letter for you from the Falcon.
So here you go.
And something about a mine?
Yes, he looks at it.
He looks at you.
He says, he looks at Corin.
Corin shrugs, pulls out a stamp, and stamps the ledger with the UBT with comedically comedically compliant.
UBT is comedically compliant.
Great.
Thanks.
Yes.
It's comedically compliant.
And then they take your receipt, stamp it again.
This time it says approved.
And then they just get up and leave.
What the hell was that?
These guys are weird.
I'm so glad that we ran into them.
Are we done counting?
Yes.
Yes, you can now go collect your money.
What money?
The receipt, the credit receipt.
You look at the letter, and it's actually for 200 gold pieces from the Neverwinner Commission.
200 gold pieces.
For the mine.
But the mine.
Is it a mine?
It's a loan.
It's a letter of credit.
No, the letter of credit was so that you could redeem the 200 gold pieces.
Oh, why am I getting it?
I don't understand why they're paying me 200 gold pieces for our mine that we owing.
Remember that you've got some gold from us?
Yeah.
The Neverwinter Commission owns the mine.
Okay.
What's his name?
Don Juan was simply intelligent.
Oh, somehow I did not know that.
So we don't own it.
That's what you're talking about.
No, you own a share in the mine.
I thought we were the owners.
Okay.
I guess I discussion.
Yeah, the Falcon and Don Juan.
So the 200 is a dividend, or we're selling our shares.
It's a dividend.
Do we agree that this is fair trade gold?
Yes.
We own the mine and therefore the mine's.
The mine wasn't.
Yeah, it wasn't ill-gotten treasure.
It was pulled from the earth.
There's no right entitled to it.
Our shares are something we received in response.
What do you mean?
We cleaned up the mine, we resumed business there.
We set them up with cheese.
Yeah.
Yeah, but we've done some work here.
We deserve we're not the ones who put it in the ground.
We happen to take it out of the ground.
All right, you're taking it too far.
Wait, wait, wait.
So if you eat a potato, is that an ill-gotten potato because it came out of the ground?
I just have to understand.
Who gave you your money?
So just to be clear, just to be clear, Buker didn't.
It is a legitimate free trade arrangement because you did it legally above board.
There was no coercion involved.
Well, pressure is legal too.
Yes, but this was a proper business.
I'm just telling you, like, based on the clear, that was your reasoning before, Vukradin.
I'm just going to go with that.
The employees were paid?
Yeah.
And they performed work.
Which resulted in goods?
All right.
Solve the labor dispute that got them to work.
That's not honest money.
Then you have to tell me what is because labor.
We did put labor in to get this business rolling.
Management labor.
Yeah, we put all that.
The hardest and most valuable type of labor.
Management.
Yes.
I feel like the bourgeois own the means of production.
All right.
I will let Valphine record the entry.
I'm recording it as fair trade gold.
We could give some of it to charity that makes you happy.
Your share?
Sure.
Your share.
Whatever.
I'm going to roll in gold with my bathrobe business anyway.
You know, Andre and Medina are going to make me rich.
What I'm hearing is if you don't assemble the bathrobes yourself.
So.
All right.
Okay.
So, yes.
All right.
I heard something about an evil house.
Is that where we should go next?
Find out what the business is with them.
Yes.
I thought we were doing a performance at the church.
That's at dawn of whatever the next appropriate day is.
Okay.
And what time is it right now?
It was the end of the day, so we can start the next day unless you want to do something else today.
I mean, I'm thirsty.
I can get my soup.
The soup is.
Apparently, we have 200 gold pieces.
Exactly.
That's a bad soul.
200 gold.
Not enough, my friend.
Not enough.
It's not enough.
I think I think a little evening visit to House.
Yeah.
Really?
Should be fun.
Yeah, yeah.
Then we can go and have dinner.
I don't want to meet with those guys.
Why not?
It'll be fun.
They're evil.
You don't know that yet.
I've got a bad feeling about them.
Ser Kaelen told me to stay away.
I'll accept it.
So, what was our business with them other than what Andre just told me?
Remember, they tried to scam the rightful owner of the brooch.
Remember last session?
Yes.
They extorted him.
Like another.
Yeah.
So that, yeah.
All right.
So as you leave the sorry, I presume you're leaving the counting house, yes?
Yeah, I think we're done here.
All right.
Stay with me.
I can't find anything about this house.
What's the name?
What?
In the quest journal.
Can't find anything about this house Marcaster.
They are in there.
I thought they were in there.
Yeah.
Which one?
Elara Seasong Meliamne.
Return statue from Lighthouse to our collector Neverwinter before House Marcaster attacks us.
And how do you see where the gauntlet is to think?
Where do you see it?
It's in the green.
The green one.
Why is it crossed over, though?
I haven't seen it.
Because we returned.
So it's done.
Yeah.
And then they extorted it, extorted money out of her brother.
Right.
So what you've discovered about House Margaster is that they've also made an offer to Vukradin as a more efficient redistributor of lost goods.
And they made an offer to Brewbarry to increase the profit margins on his business.
No, they didn't make an offer on Brewbarry.
The banker pointed out that they have the cheapest distribution network these days.
Yeah, because they're criminals.
That is your interpretation.
Well, we witnessed extortion, right, and forgery.
We witnessed that.
Yes.
So that's good.
Witnessed it.
As a banker would say, that was one bad apple.
So what's the connection with Lenine here and our supply chain?
So Lenin was trying to, so what happened was you went to the banker and Lenine was saying we can arrange it all through Lionel Castor, Lionshield Coster, right?
Yeah.
And so the banker was trying to be helpful, but Brewbarry didn't want to be helped.
You know, this was very comedic by suggesting that House Margaster is a cheaper option.
But Brewbarry didn't, Brewbarry showed his loyalty to his tribe.
Yeah, I was going to say, sorry for being loyal.
No, no, no, no, no.
Yes, I know.
This was conflicting with accounting house's obsession with profit margins.
Right.
Yeah, they're only loyal to money.
I'm not.
Yes.
And so that, and so they were trying to put ship, they weren't, they don't, he didn't care whether you are or are not going to work with House Margaster.
He's just pointing out that you would get better rates from them.
Okay, that's a nice story, GM, but you haven't answered my question.
What's the connection with Lenin's supply chain issue?
Well, so the connection is that you, what you do know is that some time ago, the whatever manifold, the displacement device you've heard under different names stopped working.
And as a result, folks haven't, the Lionshield coster hasn't been able to ship goods the way they used to.
So, Brewbarry, let me try to spell it out for you, right?
We know that there is this criminal enterprise that is in competition with your preferred distributor.
So, a hypothesis is that they sabotaged that competitor in order to drive more business to them.
No shit, Sherlock.
The question is: what are we going to do about it?
Well, do you want to protect your loyal distributor or do you want to flip, or do you want to flip on and work or do you want to help the ones who stab them in the back?
You really have to ask me this question.
Exactly.
Let's get it done before dinner.
That's what I said.
You're like, you want to attack?
No, I want to intimidate them and let them know that if they continue to fuck with my business, then they will be fucked.
They're not going to stop just because you told them to stop.
Yeah, they're Kenyans.
You're going to have to.
You're going to be.
I'm a barbarian, not a thief.
I don't work in the shadow.
Oh, you don't have to steal.
I let my enemies say that I am there and that they will suffer my wrath.
So let's do that.
Okay.
We're level seven.
We're about to be level dead.
That's fine.
Okay.
Sure.
Do you have any like magic items or allies?
I'm pretty sure they've got like the city guard in their pocket.
You know, they're going to call other people to defend.
They're going to have allies.
We're not going to have anybody.
And probably Lord Devor as well.
Yeah, probably the Lord will take their side.
We might get expelled from the city.
As a business, UBT will not be a thing.
The whole business will fall apart.
You will lose the money to build the accounting, to build the business.
Why?
And you won't be able to sell back.
You will be banned and all of your assets seized.
Well, you know, they do what they do.
I'll do what I do.
They think they can disrupt my partner's business.
So can I.
He's a barbarian, guys.
Maybe we just could.
I'm just going to do something rather than the direct approach.
Maybe we could do some stabbing in the back.
Well, I'm a barbarian.
I don't stab in the back.
I cut your head while looking at you.
So let me go and make my threats and be the judge of whether or not they are a nuisance.
And if I decide that they are, then I'll look into how to make them change their behavior by doing what I need to do.
I'm not sure.
I feel like there's no stopping the man.
Not a fan of Mr.
Philip.
You're not a fan.
So just to put Brewbarry,
even you know impossible odds, but going to intimidate is definitely something you could try to do.
Exactly.
All right.
So we'll go with the intimidation.
You want to go with the walk-in and yeah, yeah, he's an evil, bad guy.
He's not going to help himself, and he's going to try and rub my nose into it and give me some serious lead on what I can do to, you know, annoy him.
Okay.
If Brewbarry wants to do an intimidation, I will back him up and also try to intimidate.
My good friend and best fan.
All right.
So we go knock on the house, Mark.
Hold on, hold on.
Before you get there.
Before you get there, a gentleman approaches himself and introduces himself as Perrin.
Oh, God, like, why did they pick this name so that I could always be Alligander?
So for those, so for those of you who recall, the Alliganders were Lady Alligander, it was a high-ranking member, was a high-ranking family in Neverwinter.
None of you know this, but the more important point was that she was the grave that had the fireballs.
She's the owner of the necklace of fireballs?
Hold on, hold on.
And Ser Kaelen had told you that there was a lead for someone in when you wanted to return it to the rightful owners, and that the rightful owners we declared were fire and blood quest.
Return the necklace of fireballs to Alligander, the rightful owner.
Right.
And so he steps back.
He's not.
He's not smooth.
He's a man in his 30s and decent but unfashionable codes and unfashionable clothes.
And he definitely looks like he's been waiting to see, waiting for you guys for a few hours.
He goes, forgive me.
You're the ones from Phandalin?
We be.
Did you say maybe or yes?
Said we be.
Okay.
I'm sorry, my name is Perrin, Perrin Alligander.
The recovery wrote to me.
They said you'd found.
He pauses, very anxious.
He looks very uncomfortable.
My family lost something a long time ago.
Grave robbers a generation back.
We never stopped looking and they wrote to me last 10 days and since someone had it and that they were coming here and I've read the letter about 40 times.
Yes, the necklace.
We have to make sure we're giving it to the right person.
Can you prove its lineage?
Or at least start with his passport.
He goes, well, I think that this is absolutely.
Yes, I think we should do a proper transfer with all of the paperwork handled in just the right way.
Okay.
But not here.
So you asked about proper lineage.
Yes.
We have a personal banker at the counting house.
We can go there.
He's not that good at his job, though.
People at least well enough to possibly bet the lineage.
I'm not sure.
No, no, so he goes.
At the mention of the word lineage, at the mention of the word lineage, you suddenly you notice a fire in his eye, like something, something clicks, and he goes, he goes.
The camera zooms in.
Yeah, the camera's in.
Dun dun dun.
Very dramatic zoom right then.
Yes.
Hold on.
The camera zooms in.
It adds 15 pounds.
All right.
He goes.
He starts to explain.
He starts to articulate how, you know, that the alliganders used to be the first family of Neverwinter and that imposter, never member, and his lineage has taken the city from them and imposed.
We're talking about the necklace here.
Yes, no, and he's saying that the necklace is a symbol, a symbol of those who reject the Nevermember line, and that with that symbol, he will be able to rally the forces who oppose his dictatorial high taxation regime.
I yawned very loudly.
Are you telling me you're going to start a revolution with the necklace?
I don't know if I want that on my hands.
He goes, no, I'm not going to start a revolution.
No, no.
This is a symbol.
I'm not about the revolution.
This is just a symbol.
Well, it's your necklace.
Assuming you can establish your identity, et cetera, et cetera.
Yeah, I mean, if this necklace is the symbol that you say it is, I'd imagine a lot of people would lie to claim it's theirs.
Sounds, yeah, that's a good point.
Well said.
All right.
Then, just so he goes, so just as he's standing there, you notice somebody step out of the shadows.
Well, not step out of the shadows.
You've noticed him for some moments.
How many people are going to get in our pass?
You guys are like a little bit.
I mean, just to be clear, you guys have become somewhat of a local legend, right?
This is what happens when you get between 50.
Maybe we should have office hours, you know, and people ticket.
What we get for just trouncing around without bodyguards, without sunglasses, the paparazzi start following you.
Obviously, I say this.
But let's just be clear.
We have a six-foot-something guy who looks like a Goliath dressed in.
He's got like a 30-foot reach.
He's a Goliath.
Right, right.
And we've got a turtle, and we've got with the staff of Meryl, and we've got a drow cleric of Lathander whose eyes glow with the blessing of Lathander.
You're not exactly inconspicuous.
Yeah, but I mean, this isn't Houston, Texas.
This is never winter in the Forgotten Realms.
We can't be the only party looking like this.
Yeah, there's no way that you can.
But you guys are the new guys.
Okay.
You're the fashion system.
What is this guy emerging from the shadows want?
He produces a paper.
Of course, he does.
He says that he's the rightful owner of the necklace.
How antique.
And that it belongs to Dun Dun Dun House Marcaster.
Please don't be.
No, no, no, no.
Okay.
No, that's actually not what happens.
Which part?
The House Marcaster or the papers produced?
Or both.
Sorry, Marcaster.
I keep.
Yeah.
All right.
So he produces a piece of paper that, yes, once again, is sealed with the paperwork of House Margaster, proving that Perrin Allogander is in fact the rightful owner of said necklace of fireballs.
Oh.
I mean, either he just walks around with this is the one vouching for Alligander.
Well, that's a twist.
And so he produces the paper and says, and suggests that, you know, that everything is copacetic, everything is completely above board.
But if they really, if you really, really insist on making a fuss over this, we could always head over to House Margaster at our official offices where we can present to you the full lineage.
I mean, Brewbarry wants to go to the house.
Brewbarry wanted to go there anyway.
But if you intimidate them, I'm okay with conjoining these objectives.
We might have to sequence them, though.
We might need to handle the necklace and then do the intimidation.
I think that's fine.
I mean, it's still one trip.
Honestly, I kind of do the intimidation.
Brewbarry's going to go straight for the intimidation.
Well, I'm okay with him doing it first.
And as a result, we'll see what happens with the necklace.
Exactly.
Maybe we can use it as leverage.
Or we can use it.
The fixer.
Just look away.
The House Margaster guy says, pauses and says, you know, and he looks at the time and says, it's going to be late.
Could we just not just do this right here?
I give you the...
This is an official piece of paper.
No, let's head over.
You know, we've got time.
Day's not over.
We were headed there anyway.
Yeah, why don't you come with us?
Yeah.
Well, I grab him by the neck and I say, no, you're coming.
Yeah, I think he'll definitely be coming with us.
All right.
Show the way.
Okay, so you're grabbing him.
Scruffing him.
It's not kidnapping.
No, we're taking him.
I want to be clear.
We're just, you know, supporting him.
Exactly.
We don't want him to fall down.
At this point in time, Boney opens his mouth.
Boney.
Boney?
Where the hell is he?
Yes, don't forget Boney was Lady Allegander's.
No, he's been in the city with you guys.
You're outside.
Canonically, you're outside, right?
Yes.
Boney doesn't go to the building.
This is fine.
He's with us.
Yeah, he's with us.
And Boney, at this point in time, adopts a huffing and puffing kind of pose.
I mean, as much as a skeletal horse.
No lungs or anything.
And looks at him and says, you are a member of the Alagondars?
He goes, yeah.
He goes, and who exactly did this necklace belong to?
Right.
Because Boney obviously knows exactly who the necklace belonged to and the lineage and whatnot.
Because, you know, from the Alliance.
But.
Yeah, go on.
And it's quite clear.
Let me see.
He goes, Perrin looks at him and goes,
he goes, well, it was, see, you know, I can't really.
Well, it was, you immediately get the sense that he doesn't quite know all of the facts.
On top of which, Boney knows the fact that the necklace wasn't stolen until very recently when a certain Vukradin decided to return it.
And so Perrin's story has some holes in it.
Yeah.
You get him, Boney.
So, Boney is like, Boney is very skeptical about the authenticity of this Alagondar's claim to being the rightful owner of said necklace and is very dubious about the claims about how it got lost and whatnot.
I mean, that makes sense.
Let's find out if this paper really comes from House Morgaster.
And if they say that it does, then let's use Boney as a witness to expose them as frauds.
I'm sure it talks about how that'll hold up in court.
I'm sure it's a skeletal horse.
I'm sure it comes from them.
That doesn't mean it's any kind of legitimate.
He's got weapons.
All right.
Okay.
I just wanted you to know that the Boney does, you know, Boney does express, but then Boney then goes and says, but I have been dead for some time.
Not that long.
He pauses.
Well, dead is a relative term.
I mean, I was a bony creature.
Oh, Boney.
I prefer the termy instead of the Google.
He goes, I prefer the term recently unalived.
Bony's a zoomer.
Terrible.
The algorithm has saved him from demonetization.
What?
Exactly.
Unalive is used to avoid demonetization.
That's all.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
That's why I started laughing.
It took me a second to catch up with you, man.
All right.
Okay.
So does somebody else emerge from the shadows?
Are we on the way to House Morgaster?
Nobody else claiming lineage or ownership here.
No, no, nobody else is claiming lineage.
Perrin, though, after Boney makes his accusations, insists that he has all the paperwork necessary and will produce it if necessary, and that his agent points to the fixer, has already can provide that information as well.
But you'd have to go to the notary to get that information.
Everybody works for the Morgasters.
You can have as many papers as you want.
If Boney says you're not kosher, then you're not kosher.
Boney pauses and says, Mr.
Brewbarry, and he goes, Brewbarry, Brewbarry, Brewbarry Burger.
I simply can point out that there are holes in the story.
I can't really say whether he is or is not.
I did not, as you know, I spent some time in a tomb.
Yes, Boney.
Do you know who the necklace belongs to?
Yes or no?
It belonged to Lady Alagondar.
And if he indeed is a member of the Alagondar clan, it is entirely possible that he has a rightful claim to it.
And therefore, and all of a sudden you realize that Boney, among many of his other unbelievably cute traits, is an obsessed about lineages and parents and grandparents and he follows the royal families, as it were.
Yeah, he follows the royal family.
Who's born to whom?
What the rights of succession are.
He goes, well, if you're stuck in a tomb for a few hundred years, you start to do research.
Makes sense.
There were records in there, like new ones?
Oh, there was a few.
I mean, you're also, yes, there was a few.
I mean, it was a tomb, right?
So there was.
Yeah, oh, right.
New corpses.
The records were corpses.
It was a tomb.
So that's how you studied it.
I'm slow to talk about it.
I understand the motivation.
You have to explain to me the logistics of it.
I don't know how Boney Horse can do some research in books and stuff.
He's not doing bad on books.
He's doing it on the gravestones themselves.
Yes.
So he could see, like, you know, here lies X, you know, married to Y.
Here lies Lady Alagondar married to Pen Graw, you know, whatever.
All right.
Okay.
So we have a couple of choices.
You can take the night and go back, or you want to go head straight to House Morgaster.
Head straight.
Morgaster.
We've got our friends with us.
Yeah, we're dragging him along.
In the evening at night, maybe?
I mean, that's fantastic.
Good plan.
Yeah.
Exactly.
They want a concert.
Let's go.
All right.
Excuse me.
Stefan.
Yes.
Add to your character Elven Chainmail.
Because we might end up in some combat here.
Add to my character what?
Elvin Chainmail.
Elven Chainmail.
Okay.
Yeah.
And that replaces your scale mail.
Manage inventory.
Items.
Elvin Chainmail.
All right.
You arrive at equipment.
Okay.
So you arrive the guy who's with Perrin is, you know, kind of says, well, if we're going to go get this, let's go get it done properly.
And so he kind of like tries to get you to stop holding him.
Sure, Brewbarry grips is nice and gentle.
It tries to.
Try is a key word here.
It can try.
Yeah.
After trying for a few moments, he just gives up.
Meanwhile, you know, the fact that you're dressed like Brewbarry and acting like a barbarian is like not causing anybody like, but you know, there's a bunch of Brewbarry lookalikes who are like really impressed with your commitment to the bit.
Good to know.
As they say on Mandalore, this is the way.
All right.
You arrive at a notary house.
We're going to the Morgasters.
Yeah.
I know he said we could do that, but we're just dragging him back home to get the paperwork, right?
Right, right.
And, well, so it turns out that the so as you walk in, he explains that this notary house belongs to the Morgasters.
No shit.
Yes.
What doesn't?
What don't they control?
It's easier in the forest, guys.
None of this crap.
They don't control the Order of the Gauntlet.
No, they don't.
They don't.
They will soon.
Well, I'm sure they're trying.
Yeah.
So System D of Neverwinter.
So I'd like to look around.
Do I see anything like obviously, I guess not obviously, or subtly amiss, signs of criminal activity, forgery, deception?
Meth Lab just out in the open.
You know, 13 investigation.
Maybe Gary could look too.
How about a 20 insight and then
wait?
Wait, what?
I think double roll.
You got a nine perception?
It looks like I had a nine perception.
Yeah, we're going with the insight role.
20 insights.
Anybody else want to look around?
Oh, sure.
The notary?
Come on.
Did that roll?
Where's the.
All right.
So
It is, in fact, just a notary.
It doesn't have any of the usual, you know, Morgaster, you know, demonic.
So all the forgeries happen off-site.
Yes.
They're just notarized here.
They notarize forgeries.
Got it.
Okay.
This is not forgery central.
Right.
They make the paperwork to legitimize their business ventures.
Yes.
So you arrive at the notary.
And the notary is very pleased to see you.
He asks you to sit down and he says, so how can I be of assistance?
Perrin explains, well, the family of this, he points to you guys, have brought an artifact that belongs to me and has been notarized.
And the other guy shows the paperwork that demonstrates the notarization.
And Perrin says, with this official document, the necklace, the heirloom that belonged to my family, the symbol of the true rightful heirs of Neverwinter will be recognized.
But how do we know that this is the gentleman who says he is?
I mean, anybody can impersonate anybody.
He could be a polymorph for all we know.
Yeah.
Disguised selfish.
So the name.
The notary.
Sorry, I'm trying to keep all these characters in my head in my head.
The notary says, well, it's quite clear here, right?
And he shows you, he pulls out the book, which is titled Genealogy of the Alagondars.
And he says, this was verified with the usual procedures against forgeries, doppelgangers, miscellaneous magic using the threefold rule of coordinating between three different sources of conflicting evidence with different provenance.
And you can clearly see that Perrin Alagondar is, in fact, a descendant, a rightful descendant of Lady Alagondar.
And that if this is indeed stolen goods, as he claims, he absolutely deserves to have it back.
No, I got that.
I agree.
But how do I know he's Perrin Alagondar?
Oh, well, I mean, he looks like a Perrin.
Sorry.
Oh, like, how do we?
Well, he goes, the house, he goes, well, if that is your concern, I think that is utterly a reasonable concern.
At which point, the guy who holds a paperbook, well, there's a very simple solution, Mr.
Vukradin.
And this is a very common problem that we've seen with many folks in Neverwinter when they're making these kinds of deals.
And this is, by the way, such a deal.
This is why House Morgaster acts as the honest broker on the return of such goods.
So we're supposed to take your word for it.
No, no.
He was exactly.
You don't have to take his word.
They're giving us insurance.
We're taking Morgaster's word for it.
It's title insurance.
That's all it is.
How can I lose?
That's what we call bullshit.
You can't really guarantee anything, but if it's wrong, we'll take care of you.
So actually, he's very confused about the social title insurance, but you can see his eyes clicking, going, this might be an interesting scam we could pull in the future.
Charge thousands of dollars.
They'll never even know.
They'll just sign it because, hey, who cares?
Title insurance.
Can they also give an extended warranty on this necklace?
As long as we're here.
The notary says, all these flavors of insurance are, I'm sure, are could definitely be products that could be offered in the future.
But in the present, what we could do is we could keep the necklace in layaway in House Morgaster's warehouses.
Not happening.
All right.
Until you can produce three independent, independent from House Morgaster, witnesses as to who you really are, and it proves to us that you are who you say you are, then you can take a walk and forget about the necklace.
Thank you very much.
Now onto other businesses.
Remember the intimidation?
Yes.
Yeah, we're going to the Morgasters.
Yes, exactly.
So the easiest way to go to the Morgasters is to give the necklace.
No, no, no.
We can just walk there.
Oh, you're going to walk there?
All right.
So you're telling Perrin he's not getting the necklace, and you're telling the other guy he's not getting the necklace.
No, but they're coming with us.
Yeah.
We want to settle this at the source.
The notary could come too if he'd like.
No, the better.
The more allies Morgasters have, the better for us.
We need you to have more characters to track.
And more enemies for us to fight.
Comments is going to be too easy.
You know, we have yet to take over the Spire of the Morning Lord to have more allies.
Just noting that.
Actually, that would be.
Maybe we should recruit some more allies.
This is going to be a pretty.
This battle is going to be pretty one-sided.
We're just going to threaten the crime.
And then we can take care of it.
We're threatening and then we're fleeing.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
Yes.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
So as you're heading past, as you're heading towards the House Morgaster, you canonically, of course, because in City Adventures, players can go any which way they want.
So the GM has to simply declare you pass by.
I have learned this over the last two years.
You pass by a building
as you're headed towards House Morgaster, a business establishment near the docks, a dead displacement, a building that looks shut down.
And as you notice it, there's a civic notice nailed to the door.
Okay, what's on the notice?
What does the notice say?
It says displacement.
No, it declares that this building has been shut down until further notice by order of Lord Neverember and that the services provided by the services provided for instantaneous shipping have been closed until further so you get the impression that this is perhaps where the manifold was housed.
Yeah.
Okay, does this berry guy know anything about this?
Why did they close down this establishment?
This fine establishment, I might add.
Lucrative establishment.
Who are you asking?
Perrin?
No, Perrin's no cliff.
Oh, Perrin.
Perrin simply says that it stopped working.
Nobody knows quite why it stopped working.
And that this, and then he pauses and says that this is probably, he goes on some revolutionary tirade about how the Neverwinter Commission has its hands in everything and controls everything.
And because it controls everything, they probably shut it down so they can, so that the cheap and easy way to ship goods would be turned into a mechanism of control, etc.
How convenient for House Morgaster, isn't it?
He said the Neverwinter Commission.
Yes.
Haven't we been invited by Lord Neverwinter to have?
The same commission that paid us for the mine?
Yes.
Great.
I'm starting to see your point.
Yeah.
They have wield their influence flagrantly.
The Neverwinter Commission.
You could ask about the Neverwinter Commission, but we can keep going.
All right.
I happen to think that undermining power structures is best done behind the scenes.
Okay.
Very well.
All right.
Yeah, it would be guys if they don't know that we're doing this.
They'll probably know.
Just like they don't need evidence that they know.
They don't need evidence or a reason to disappear anyone.
Well, they got to know who it is.
Otherwise, that person doesn't have any leverage.
You let them know.
Not make it obvious.
I love having Brewbarry.
Then you sabotage.
Then they know where it's coming from.
They're supposed to sit at the table.
I truly love you, man.
This is fantastic.
This is awesome.
This is great.
I love it.
I'm totally here for you.
All right.
So you're at the Morgaster's Logistic Operations Eastern Quay.
And you're dragging, you know, I guess at this point in time, Perrin.
Notary.
Perrin.
The notary has, unless the notary did not come with you.
All right.
Okay.
As you, the operation looks, it looks like it's a well-run operations.
Why don't we roll some insight or investigation checks?
Let's see if I can't flub this one.
Gary, I think.
Oh, wow.
Even worse.
What did you get, Gary?
Sorry, I don't want to roll 20 up right now.
Only 21.
Okay, well, so fine.
I can't.
Soma notices that it's clean.
Well kept.
Yes, very, very, very impressively cleaned and organized.
On the other hand, Valphine, whose family was involved in all sorts of, shall we refer to it as trade.
Moving goods, right, is able to quickly diagnose, is able to quickly see that this place is an extremely well-run operations.
And she notices that there's all sorts of Lion Shield labeled goods in boxes.
Lion Shield.
Yeah, Lion Shield Coster goods.
That clearly, House Morgaster.
Right.
So House Morgaster.
House Morgaster.
Yes.
So essentially, House Morgaster is now moving.
So Lion Shield didn't have a transportation service because they relied on their displacement device.
So now they're being forced to pay money to have the goods moved to Morgaster.
No, no, through Morgaster.
Morgaster's not interested in possessing the goods.
Morgaster's interested in.
Yeah, they just want the profits.
They're just so yeah, so they're definitely in the business of moving goods, not stealing goods.
I mean, at least this part, this part of the operation.
This particular apparatus is, yeah.
It's a legitimate business front.
Yes.
They're legitimately moving goods.
How they're getting all the business is less than legitimate.
And how exactly are they moving the goods?
Oh, that's a good question.
You know.
Not through displacement by any chance.
No, no, no, you know, the usual caravans with armed guards, the usual thing.
Huh.
Old school.
It sounds like a very expensive way to move goods.
And profitable.
Yes.
The only game in town.
They can charge whatever they want, no matter how expensive it is.
Again.
All right.
So again, and then your favorite guy, Colin Sharp, walks up.
Who's the Colin Sharp?
He's the guy who was in the green suit who showed up at the guy who made the deal with who extorted the broken.
Yes.
This asshole.
Okay.
Yes.
Lord Cassian, so Colin Sharp is very happy to see you and is very excited.
And says, no, no, he's, you know, he's kind of a smooth, you know, he's a smooth guy.
He's not a, you know, he's working on commission.
Yeah, yeah, he's not, he's not.
Gary, roll your insight.
Hold on, just a second.
Let me tell something.
Okay, that's what it was.
Insight.
What is it?
All right.
You beat me.
I know.
Gary, I think you have a special ability now related to your character where you can detect lies or cause people who are lying.
Oh, that's right.
Right.
I'm surprised you just wanted to remind you of it.
Thank you.
Where is that ability?
Of course, he's lying.
He's a thug.
All right.
So he says there, he goes, so he's very excited to see you.
And he goes, Ah, Mr.
Vukradin, I'm so delighted to see you.
Oh, and Mr.
Perrin, I hope everything is going that the letter of introduction we provided was sufficient.
The evidence.
And then he turns to you and says, Mr.
Vukradin, I hope you see from how we manage that we're very good at solving one of the problems that Ser Kaelen suggested you might have when he reached out to us through one of our agents that perhaps we could provide the connecting tissue between your finds and the real proprietaires using our patented system.
That's what we're here for.
So, Brewbarry, let's do some intimidation.
That's what we're here for, my good man.
Solving problems and getting your help into solving problems.
I got a 15.
What did you get, Brewbarry?
Intimidation.
Let me roll it.
Oh, God.
All right.
A six.
Awesome.
Just not very lucky.
No.
Whatever.
Let me do the talk.
You jokes, man.
You joke.
It's the rope, man.
The rope just makes you look so soft.
And, you know, that's why I was here to back you up.
15.
So, Colin, my good friend, I tap, I, you know, pat him on the back.
You're going to help us solve problems.
Do exactly what you said you would do.
So he goes, he's a first person.
So let's just be clear.
Let's just be clear.
He's not intimidated, but he's appreciating you.
He's amused by the situation.
I have a good friend of mine, you might call it a business partner who has this shipping company that was using this device that suddenly got broke.
And the house was shut down.
And then they have to rely now on your fine establishment to transport their goods.
I was wondering if you could enlighten me as to what exactly happened to this device.
Maybe you know, don't you?
And I affirm my grip on his shoulder.
Let me see.
Does he have to remember what I said?
This is.
You know, Colin, I've been told that you're quite sharp, no pun intended.
You said his name was Colin Sharp.
Colin.
So surely you know something about this.
So he, well, what he says is that you failed your intimidation check.
So he's not intimidated by you, but he simply points as my dear friend, Mr.
Brewbarry, can I call you a friend?
Of course, of course.
We are friends here.
Yes, we're all friends.
So my friend Brewbarry, the device you're referring to was run by House.
Was not run by House Mark Gaster.
We were not involved with the operation of that thing.
And perhaps if we had been, it would not have gotten damaged and been no longer operable.
To be honest with you, I don't think I know what happened, although I do know that there was some gnome that was hired to attempt to fix it.
And as a result of the attempts to fix it or was it improve its operation, it stopped working.
Might you have the name of this GNOME job?
I'm sorry.
I wouldn't have surely a man of your knowledge.
Well, you know, I just pauses and says, see, perhaps if you were to come tomorrow or we were to resolve some, we were to enter into a business arrangement, I would be more inclined.
27 persuasion.
He goes, Mr.
Vukradin, Mr.
Vukradin, I think, you know, I'd love to help.
In fact, I will help, but I don't have the information.
I personally don't have the information.
I'll have to ask around.
So if you're willing to come tomorrow, I will give it to you.
But can we go back to the...
With that lot going on tomorrow, so we've got a concert.
Do you think you guys could come to the concert?
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah, because it's a benefit.
It's a benefit.
And we really want lots of people to come and donate to this important cause.
Do you think you could get the whole house to come?
I don't think I could do that, but I'm certain I, as a representative of the house, would be more than delighted to show up.
That would be excellent.
Well, better than nobody.
Something, yeah.
He may not be the only person to show up, but I'm just.
May also suggest that you may see this as a business opportunity.
I mean, should we get this device working again?
And, you know, I've heard it's quite brilliant at transporting goods at a very cheap rate.
This could be a business opportunity.
We're not doing that.
Of course, we're not.
But it doesn't hurt to suggest that.
You're deceiving them.
Is that what's going on, Brewbarry?
Sidebar?
Yes.
Okay.
Got it.
Deception.
Roll your deception.
God damn it.
Why do we have to roll dice all the time?
Deception.
No, no, I'm just.
Come on, one.
I roll polar.
He doesn't notice.
He doesn't notice the lie.
He thinks you're just being a barbarian who doesn't know what he's talking about.
Exactly.
Seems fine.
Perfect cover.
And I don't think that's good, by the way.
We'll take that.
All right, guys.
I got to go to bed.
You find out who the GNOME is for me.
You find out exactly what happened.
I have a feeling I know who the gnome is.
Because, you know, machines get broke, all supply chains get disrupted, things happen.
Shit does break.
Right.
By the way, just so we're just so we're on the same page.
Next.
And the parent and the fixer are the parent and the guy with the paperwork are still there and they want the necklace of fireballs.
So they know what they got to do.
Produce three independent witnesses that can guarantee who he is.
Okay, so that's what you want.
All right.
So and House Mark Gaster is suggesting that you can hand over the necklace of fireballs to them for safekeeping, and you've decided not to go down that route.
Exactly.
Why would we need to do that?
We brought it all this way.
Okay.
We are the guy of the necklace.
Yeah.
Not House Mark Gaster.
It's much safer with us.
Yes.
Right.
You do notice.
Yeah.
The guy who's got that who produced the paperwork looks a little bit unhappy.
Yeah, I take the paperwork, I make a little paper ball with it, and then I toss it over my shoulder.
You're always egging him on, man.
Is that making it crystal clear for you, Perrin?
Yeah, yeah, just to be clear.
The guy with the paper momentarily thinks to reach for his weapon, choose, and Corin looks at him, and he doesn't.
Right.
Wise decision.
Now, don't make me keep that paper, that piece of paper and you know, chop, chop, move along.
Mr.
Sharp says, Mr.
The gentleman, the gentleman are sticklers for ritual and control in House Margaster.
Business is to make sure that the customer is satisfied and we will provide all the information you need.
I would like to roll a 24 perception on the paperwork.
So, okay, so the paperwork, I mean, so much for going to bed, hey, Dave.
No, no, no, no, let me, no, no, let me answer that.
The paperwork, so you do look at the paperwork, and it is, in fact, what you perceive from the paperwork is that it is authentic, all right, and that in that it does have the correct sets of information.
It's not like Perrin was lying.
I mean, Alegander has allied with Mercaster, right?
Right.
And they're trying to together overthrow Lord Neverwinter or something like that.
Could all be totally legitimate and they're still evil.
Yeah.
Right.
Just to be clear, it's the paperwork is clear.
Like it doesn't.
Yeah.
This is really.
I mean, I was looking for my position is if we can if we can establish his identity and he's the rightful owner of the necklace, we have to turn over the necklace.
If he then takes the necklace, puts it on and shoots a fireball at us.
Well, that sucks, but that's what we have to do anyway.
Yep.
All right.
So just to be clear, the paperwork is clear.
I just want to be clear.
The paperwork is clean.
Yes.
What's not clean is we don't know if he is who he says he is.
Yeah.
I mean, he, so, yeah, so he, he will, he has stuff at his house that he's happy to provide for you.
All right.
That's stuff.
We want witnesses and witnesses that aren't in House Margaster's pocket.
Oh, that he can provide that too.
Good.
I'll provide that and then you'll get what you do.
And he suggests and he suggests an inn that you guys can all meet at where he will provide all of that information.
I thought we were going to meet at House Markaster.
No, you are in House Markaster.
No, we're going to meet at the Church of Athander after the sermon.
After the sermon.
Is that where you want to meet with?
That's where we want to meet with Perrin?
Yes.
Sure.
Well, we do have to.
I definitely want to see him.
We have to do the gig.
And we have to tell the whole town the new name of the band.
All right.
Okay.
So, so, so you tell Perrin we'll meet after the church service at the Spire of the Morning Lord.
Is that what I'm hearing?
Yes, I definitely want to see him set foot within the temple.
All right.
Nice.
Okay, interesting tax.
All right.
I like that.
Okay.
So Perrin is very happy to do that.
He explains that he too is a, although not a exclusive worshiper of the Morning Lord, is a big believer in the Morning Lords.
And he starts talking about the Morning Lord as a god of good, etc., etc., etc.
Valphine, do you roll your eyes or do you keep your smile straight and just smile more teethily or just are completely blasé?
Just blase.
So I missed something before we conclude.
Is there was this other guy who was pretending that he owned the necklace?
Who was he again?
Sorry, yeah.
No, he doesn't.
He's an agent of an agent of House Margaster.
He was also an agent of House Margaster.
Well, yeah.
Everyone in town is.
Yeah, so we need to find out.
Next session, we need to find out who is not with House Markaster, and we need to align with those people just in case, I think.
All right.
Okay.
All right, guys.
Bye.
All right.